Register of the Rodney Kennedy-Minott Papers, 1967-1994
Hoover Institution Archives
Rodney Kennedy-Minott Papers,
1967-1994
90010
Hoover Institution Archives
29 manuscript boxes, 17 envelopes, 1 phonotape cassette (13.7 linear feet)
Correspondence, memoranda, reports, notes, printed matter, photographs, and sound recordings relating to the 1967 congressional campaign of Paul McCloskey in California, McCloskey's 1972 Republican presidential primary campaign, the 1976 presidential campaign of Jimmy Carter (especially in California), American foreign policy during the presidential administration of Jimmy Carter, and United States relations with Sweden. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Kennedy-Minott, Rodney
Access
Collection is open for research. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items, computer media, and digital files. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos, films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1990.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Alternate Forms Available
Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Biographical note
1928, June 1 Born, Portland, Oregon
1950-1952 Served with the United States Army
1953 B.A., Stanford University
1956 M.A., Stanford University
1960 Ph.D., Stanford University
1960-1961 Instructor in History, Stanford University
1961-1962 Assistant Professor, Assistant Director, History of Western Civilization Program, Stanford University
1962 Author, Peerless Patriots: The Organized Veterans and the Spirit of Americanism
1962-1963 Assistant Director, Summer Session, Western Civilization Program, Stanford University
1963-1965 Director, Summer Session, Western Civilization Program, Stanford University
1964 Author, The Fortress That Never Was: The Myth of Hitler's Bavarian Stronghold
1965-1966 Associate Professor, Portland State University; Congressional Staff Member
1966-1967 Associate Professor, Associate Dean, Instruction, California State University, Hayward
1967-1969 Division Head, Humanities, California State University, Hayward
1968 Author, The Sinking of the Lollipop: Shirley Temple vs. Pete McCloskey
1969-1975 Professor, California State University, Hayward
1971 Author, "In the Name of Democracy Bring Back Bossism", Report on Democratic Party Reform, California Democratic State Central Committee's Reform Commission, Sacramento
1977-1980 Ambassador to Sweden and Chairman, Swedish Fulbright Commission
1981 Adjunct Professor, Monterey Institute of International Studies, California
1981-1982 Senior Research Scholar, Hoover Institution
1982-1983 Executive Vice President, Direction International, Washington D.C.
1983 Chairman, Alpha International, New York City
1986 Senior Fellow, Center for International and Strategic Affairs, University of California, Los Angeles
1986- Senior Research Fellow, Hoover Institution, Stanford University
1988 Author, The Far North: The Tension Point
U.S. Regional Force Application: The Maritime Strategy and its Effect on Nordic Stability
1989 Author, Tension in the North: Sweden and Nordic Security
1990 Distinguished Guest Lecturer for National Security Affairs, U.S. Naval Postgraduate School, Monterey, California
1990 Author, Lonely Path To Follow: Nonaligned Sweden, United States/NATO, and the USSR
Scope and Contents note
Correspondence, memoranda, reports, notes, printed matter, photographs, and sound recordings relating to the 1967 congressional campaign of Paul McCloskey in California, McCloskey's 1972 Republican presidential primary campaign, the 1976 presidential campaign of Jimmy Carter (especially in California), American foreign policy during the presidential administration of Jimmy Carter, and United States relations with Sweden.
Carter, Jimmy, 1924-; Democratic Party (U.S.); McCloskey, Paul N., 1927-; Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); United States. Congress. House.; United States. Department of State.; Audiotapes.; California--Politics and government--1951-; Diplomats--United States.; Presidents--United States--Election--1972.; Presidents--United States--Election--1976.; Sweden--Foreign relations--United States.; Sweden.; United States--Foreign relations--1977-1981.; United States--Foreign relations--Sweden.; United States--Foreign relations.; United States--Politics and government--1945-1989.; United States--Politics and government.
- Biographical file
  Scope and Contents note
  Biographical sketches, awards and honors, curriculum vitae, clippings, printed matter, press release, correspondence, personal financial records, travel information, family announcements, social invitations and miscellaneous records relating to the life of Rodney Kennedy-Minott, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - Biographical sketches (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Awards and honors (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Curriculum vitae (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - Clippings (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Printed matter (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Press release (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Personal financial records (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Personal travel documents (Box-folder 1: 8)
  - Family announcements (Box-folder 1: 9)
  - Social invitations and greetings cards (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 1: 11)
- Speeches and Writings, 1968-1990
  Notes, remarks, printed matter, published essays, books, working paper by Rodney Kennedy-Minott, arranged chronologically
  - Speech, delivered by Rodney Kennedy-Minott, translated in Swedish, undated (Box-folder 1: 12)
  - Speech, delivered at the Republican Electronic Data Processing Conference, undated (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - "Notes on Vietnem,", 1968 December 3 (Box-folder 1: 14)
  - "Introduction," Jorden Runt, (includes two printed copies), 1977 (Box-folder 1: 15)
  - "The U.S. Man in Sweden," remarks, Aftonbladet, 1977 October 4 (Box-folder 1: 16)
  - Remarks for students, V-Dala Nation, Uppsala, 1978 April 27 (Box-folder 1: 17)
  - Briefing Remarks to Codel Hawkins, 1978 August 28 (Box-folder 1: 18)
  - Speech, portions delivered at British Women's Club luncheon, (most of the speech given to Sallskapet Stockholmsakademikerna Group, Dec. 22, 1978), 1979 February 29 (Box-folder 1: 19)
  - Economic Speech, 1979 March 5 (Box-folder 1: 20)
  - Introductory remarks delivered to the Oakland-Berkeley Chapter of the World Affairs Council, 1981 June 2 (Box-folder 1: 21)
  - "Technology Transfer: An Overview," speech, 1982 October (Box-folder 1: 22)
  - U.S. Regional Force Application: The Maritime Strategy and its Effects on Nordic Stability, 1988 (Box-folder 1: 23)
  - Tension in the North: Sweden and Nordic Security, Working Paper No. 70, Center for International and Strategic Affairs, University of California, Los Angeles, 1989 July (Box-folder 1: 24)
  - Lonely Path To Follow: Nonaligned Sweden, United States/NATO, and the USSR, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 25)
- Political campaigns file, 1967-1977
  Includes correspondence, clippings, budget, donations, printed matter, press release, telegrams, memoranda, reports, map, schedules, magazines relating to the Congressional campaign of Pete McCloskey vs. Shirley Temple Black, 1967-1969, Presidential GOP nomination campaign of 1971-1972 and Presidential campaign, election, and inauguration of Jimmy Carter, 1974-1977, arranged chronologically by physical form. Includes a few letters neither from nor to Rodney Kennedy-Minott
  - Congressional Campaign - Pete McCloskey vs. Shirley Temple Black, 1967-1969
    - Correspondence
      - General (Box-folder 2: 1)
      - Burns, James MacGregor, 1969 (Box-folder 2: 2)
      - Cranston, Alan, 1969 (Box-folder 2: 3)
      - Dunn, George E., 1969 (Box-folder 2: 4)
      - Frank, Gerald W., 1968 (Box-folder 2: 5)
      - Martinez, Al, 1968 (Box-folder 2: 6)
      - McCloskey, Paul N. Jr., M.C., 1968-1970 (Box-folder 2: 7)
      - Monaco, Dan, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 2: 8)
      - Pacelli, Francis P., 1968 (Box-folder 2: 9)
      - Powell, Mike, 1968 (Box-folder 2: 10)
      - Rodgers, William, 1969 (Box-folder 2: 11)
      - Staley, Ross, Mr.and Mrs., 1969 (Box-folder 2: 12)
      - Van Aken, Mark J., 1968 (Box-folder 2: 13)
      - Wells, Albert, 1968 (Box-folder 2: 14)
      - Whitaker, Urban, Mr., 1968 (Box-folder 2: 15)
      - Yimm, Ken, Mr., 1968 (Box-folder 2: 16)
      - Z'berg, Edwin L., 1969 (a typescript note, by Rodney Kennedy-Minott is enclosed), July 12, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 17)
    - Printed matter (Box-folder 2: 18)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 2: 19)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 2: 20)
  - Pete McCloskey - GOP Presidential Nomination Campaign - Oregon, 1971-1972
    - Budget (Box-folder 2: 21)
    - Reports (Box-folder 2: 22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 2: 23)
  - Pete McCloskey - GOP Presidential Nomination Campaign - New Hampshire, 1971-1972
    - Printed matter / clippings (Box-folder 2: 24)
    - Schedules (Box-folder 2: 25)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 2: 26)
  - Senate Race - Pierre Salinger, 1972 (Box-folder 2: 27)
  - Jimmy Carter - Presidential Campaign, 1974-1976
    - Correspondence, 1973-1976
      - Unidentified (Box-folder 2: 28)
      - Batista, Armand J., 1975 (Box-folder 2: 29)
      - Blum, Barbara, 1976 (Box-folder 2: 30)
      - Brownridge, Kent, 1976 (Box-folder 2: 31)
      - Burton, John L., 1973 (Box-folder 2: 32)
      - Carter, Jimmy, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 2: 33)
      - Coughlan, Robert, 1976 (Box-folder 2: 34)
      - Crispin, J. Hewes, 1975 (Box-folder 2: 35)
      - Cutler, Goldie, 1976 (Box-folder 2: 36)
      - Dees, Morris, 1976 (Box-folder 2: 37)
      - Eisenstadt, Stuart, 1976 (Box-folder 2: 38)
      - Eliaser, Ann Alanson, 1975 (Box-folder 2: 39)
      - Feinstein, Dianne, 1976 (Box-folder 2: 40)
      - Gatov, Elizabeth R., 1976 (Box-folder 2: 41)
      - Gevirtz, Don L., 1976 (Box-folder 2: 42)
      - Gomperts, Robert E., 1975-1976 (Box-folder 2: 43)
      - Jordan, Hamilton, 1976 (Box-folder 2: 44)
      - Kraft, Tim, C. 1976 (Box-folder 2: 45)
      - Lipshutz, Bob, (some memoranda are enclosed), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 2: 46)
      - Maher, John, 1975 (Box-folder 2: 47)
      - McCarthy, Leo T., 1976 (Box-folder 2: 48)
      - McLaughlin, Donald H., 1975 (Box-folder 2: 49)
      - Murphy, Reg, 1976 (Box-folder 2: 50)
      - Novelli, Michael Peter, 1975 (Box-folder 2: 51)
      - O'Connell, Terry, (telephone conversation), 1976 (Box-folder 2: 52)
      - Palevsky, Max, 1973 (Box-folder 2: 53)
      - Petris, Nicholas C., 1976 (Box-folder 2: 54)
      - Powell, Joseph L., Jr., 1976 (Box-folder 2: 55)
      - Schultz, Jackson, 1975 (Box-folder 2: 56)
      - Schwartz, Robert, A.D., 1975 (Box-folder 2: 57)
      - Smith, J. Malcolm, 1976 (Box-folder 2: 58)
      - Williams, Dr., 1975 (Box-folder 2: 59)
      - Willoughby, R.E., 1975 (Box-folder 2: 60)
    - Contributions
      - General (Box-folder 2: 61)
      - 1975
        - May (Box-folder 2: 62)
        - June (Box-folder 2: 63)
        - July (Box-folder 2: 64)
        - September (Box-folder 2: 65)
        - October (Box-folder 2: 66)
    - Committees (Box-folder 3: 1)
      - Field staff (Box-folder 3: 2)
      - San Mateo County staff (Box-folder 3: 3)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 3: 4)
        - 1974 August (Box-folder 3: 5)
        - 1975 November (Box-folder 3: 6)
        - 1976 (Box-folder 3: 7)
        - March (Box-folder 3: 8)
        - July (Box-folder 3: 9)
        - August (Box-folder 3: 10)
        - September (Box-folder 3: 11)
        - October (Box-folder 3: 12)
        - November (Box-folder 3: 13)
        - 1990 July (Box-folder 3: 14)
      - Schedules, 1975
        - April (Box-folder 3: 15)
        - October (Box-folder 3: 16)
      - Donor list (Box-folder 3: 17)
      - Press release / magazines (Box-folder 3: 18)
      - Printed matter (Box-folder 3: 19)
      - Clippings (Box-folder 4: 1)
      - Social invitations (Box-folder 4: 2)
      - Telegrams (Box-folder 4: 3)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Articles, undated (Box-folder 4: 4)
        - Resume (Box-folder 4: 5)
        - Sign-Up sheet (Box-folder 4: 6)
        - Maps (Box-folder 4: 7)
      - List of names and telephone numbers (Box-folder 4: 8)
      - Leaflet and sticker (Box-folder 4: 9)
  - President-Elect, 1976-1977
    - Correspondence
      - Unidentified (Box-folder 4: 10)
      - Carter, Jimmy, 1977 (Box-folder 4: 11)
      - Christopher, Warren, 1977 (Box-folder 4: 12)
      - Feinstein, Dianne, 1977 (Box-folder 4: 13)
      - Hutcheson, Rick, 1977 (Box-folder 4: 14)
      - Jordan, Hamilton, 1977 (Box-folder 4: 15)
      - Kraft, Tim, 1977 (Box-folder 4: 16)
      - Manatt, Charles T., 1977 (Box-folder 4: 17)
      - Nemerovski, Howard N., 1977 (Box-folder 4: 18)
      - Schaefer, Philip A., 1977 (Box-folder 4: 19)
      - Strauss, Robert, 1977 (Box-folder 4: 20)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 4: 21)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 4: 22)
    - Printed matter (Box-folder 4: 23)
    - Inauguration (Box-folder 4: 24)
- Ambassador-designate office file, 1977
  Correspondence, memoranda, press release, clippings, printed matter, schedules relating to Rodney Kennedy-Minott's nomination, subsequent Senate hearings leading to his appointment and swearing-in as Ambassador to Sweden. Also includes his briefing, prior to his assumption of office, on the organization of the Embassy, office staff, staff at the Ambassador's residence, salary information for the staff and the Ambassador, travel regulations, freight allowances for the Ambassador and his family and general information about Sweden. Includes letters neither from nor to Rodney Kennedy-Minott
  - Correspondence, 1977
    - (memorandum and handwritten note are enclosed), Jan-Feb. (Box-folder 4: 25)
    - April (Box-folder 4: 26)
    - May (Box-folder 4: 27)
    - June (Box-folder 4: 28)
    - July (Box-folder 4: 29)
    - (telegram is enclosed), August (Box-folder 4: 30)
  - Clippings (Box-folder 4: 31)
  - Printed matter (Box-folder 4: 32)
  - Senate Hearings and Confirmation
    - Correspondence, (arranged alphabetically), 1977
      - Batinovich, Robert (Box-folder 5: 1)
      - Cranston, Alan (Box-folder 5: 2)
      - Madison, James R. (Box-folder 5: 3)
      - McCloskey, Paul N., Jr. (Box-folder 5: 4)
      - Nelson, David A. (Box-folder 5: 5)
      - Pell, Claiborne (Box-folder 5: 6)
      - Perry, Jack (Box-folder 5: 7)
      - Woods, Ronald E. (Box-folder 5: 8)
    - Memoranda, 1977
      - handwritten, July (Box-folder 5: 9)
      - August (Box-folder 5: 10)
    - Schedules (Box-folder 5: 11)
    - Proceedings (Box-folder 5: 12)
    - Press release (Box-folder 5: 13)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 5: 14)
    - Briefing
      - Organization and responsibilities (Box-folder 5: 15)
      - List of names of U.S. ambassadors (Box-folder 5: 16)
      - Organizational charts with handwritten notes (Box-folder 5: 17)
      - Organization and responsibilities of the American Embassy (Box-folder 5: 18)
      - Political Section, including Labor Office (Box-folder 5: 19)
      - Economic/Commercial Section (Box-folder 5: 20)
      - Agricultural Attache (Box-folder 5: 21)
      - Scientific Attache (Box-folder 5: 22)
      - Consular Section (Box-folder 5: 23)
      - Administrative Section (Box-folder 5: 24)
      - Defense Attache (Box-folder 5: 25)
      - United States Information Service (Box-folder 5: 26)
      - American Consulate in Goteborg (Box-folder 5: 27)
      - King of Sweden, with a brief biographical sketch of the King and a list of court officials (Box-folder 5: 28)
      - Post Report - Sweden, with printed matter and clippings (Box-folder 5: 29)
      - Security classifications (Box-folder 5: 30)
      - Traffic analysis (Box-folder 5: 31)
      - Diplomatic terms (Box-folder 5: 32)
      - Diplomatic mail and pouch facilities (Box-folder 5: 33)
      - Questions and answers about the American Embassy (Box-folder 5: 34)
    - Staffing and awards
      - Home State Codes (Box-folder 5: 35)
      - Foreign Service Staffing Pattern (Box-folder 5: 36)
      - Service listing (Box-folder 5: 37)
      - Staffing and awards (Box-folder 5: 38)
      - Office of Executive Director (Box-folder 5: 39)
      - Salary and allowances (Box-folder 5: 40)
      - Chief of Mission - inventory (Box-folder 5: 41)
      - Telegram (Box-folder 5: 42)
      - Memoranda (Box-folder 5: 43)
    - Sweden - Information
      - General information (Box-folder 6: 1)
      - Brochures on Swedish Parliament and diplomatic social usage (Box-folder 6: 2)
      - Bibliography of useful works in English (Box-folder 6: 3)
      - Traffic in Sweden (Box-folder 6: 4)
      - Reports on social customs (Box-folder 6: 5)
      - Art (Box-folder 6: 6)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 6: 7)
      - Clippings (Box-folder 6: 8)
      - Brochures (Box-folder 6: 9)
    - Travel
      - Travel arrangements (Box-folder 6: 10)
      - Air freight and surface shipments (Box-folder 6: 11)
      - Medical information (Box-folder 6: 12)
      - Itinerary (Box-folder 6: 13)
      - Travel authorization (Box-folder 6: 14)
- Ambassador to Sweden office file, 1977-1980
  Ambassador's credential ceremony, correspondence, memoranda, schedules, clippings, notes, printed matter, telegrams, newsletters relating to the years of Rodney Kennedy-Minott's service as Ambassador to Sweden. Also enclosed are numerous invitations to parties, concerts, art show, boat show, opera, religious services received by the Ambassador and his wife and the invitations sent out by them to various social gatherings at their residence, the Nobel Prize ceremonies and related protocol information, banquets and receptions given by the Ambassador and his wife to the Nobel Prize winning American scientists. Also includes State Department communications, documents relating to American foreign policy, remarks made by Rodney Kennedy-Minott about President Carter and printed matter regarding Carter administration in general, and Rodney Kennedy-Minott's resignation as Ambassador to Sweden. Correspondence in this series includes letters neither to nor from Rodney Kennedy-Minott
  - Credential Ceremony
    - Letter of Credence (Box-folder 6: 15)
    - Remarks (Box-folder 6: 16)
    - Memoranda (Box-folder 6: 17)
    - Clippings (includes some clippings in Swedish) (Box-folder 6: 18)
    - Printed matter (includes some in Swedish) (Box-folder 6: 19)
  - 1977
    - Correspondence
      - General (Box-folder 6: 20)
      - Unidentified (Box-folder 6: 21)
      - Ahlmark, Per (Box-folder 6: 22)
      - Beeth, Gunnar (Box-folder 6: 23)
      - Blum, Barbara (Box-folder 6: 24)
      - Cannon, Howard W. (Box-folder 6: 25)
      - Chapman, Christian, Mr. (Box-folder 6: 26)
      - Conant, Melvin A., Mr. (Box-folder 6: 27)
      - Connors, Eleanor (Box-folder 6: 28)
      - Dance, Maurice (Box-folder 6: 29)
      - Deason, Robert G. (Box-folder 6: 30)
      - Delancie, Marlene (Box-folder 7: 1)
      - Djerassi, Carl (Box-folder 7: 2)
      - Fultz, Barbara (Box-folder 7: 3)
      - Gomperts, Robert E. (Box-folder 7: 4)
      - Graham, Charles Hill (Box-folder 7: 5)
      - Groff, Gerald L., Dr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 7: 6)
      - Gustavi, Gun, Mrs. (Box-folder 7: 7)
      - Hallin, Maud (Box-folder 7: 8)
      - Hertz, Hellmuth, Prof. (Box-folder 7: 9)
      - Hubbard, John P., M.D. (Box-folder 7: 10)
      - Huss, Erik, Honorable (Box-folder 7: 11)
      - Jordan, Hamilton (Box-folder 7: 12)
      - Knapp, Charles B. (Box-folder 7: 13)
      - Kraft, Tim (Box-folder 7: 14)
      - Langan, Leon Verdin, Jr. (Box-folder 7: 15)
      - Li, Choh Hao (Box-folder 7: 16)
      - Linder, Staffan Burenstam (Box-folder 7: 17)
      - Lindstrom, Torsten, Mr. (Box-folder 7: 18)
      - Lockridge, Kenneth A., Mr. (Box-folder 7: 19)
      - Lofvist, Gunnar (Box-folder 7: 20)
      - Lokrantz, Jessie, Dr. (Box-folder 7: 21)
      - Marshall, F. Ray (Box-folder 7: 22)
      - Moose, Richard, Honorable (Box-folder 7: 23)
      - Nelson, Dave, Mr. (Box-folder 7: 24)
      - Newman, Frank (Box-folder 7: 25)
      - Nilsson, Tore (Box-folder 7: 26)
      - Ohlin, Bertil, Prof. (Box-folder 7: 27)
      - Oke, David W., Jr. (Box-folder 7: 28)
      - Osterberg, Tom (Box-folder 7: 29)
      - Owens, John P. (Box-folder 7: 30)
      - Perry, Betsy (Box-folder 7: 31)
      - Perry, Jack (Box-folder 7: 32)
      - Pers, Anders H., Mr. (Box-folder 7: 33)
      - Persson, Sune O., Mr. (a letter in Swedish is enclosed) (Box-folder 7: 34)
      - Phillips, John D. (brochure is enclosed) (Box-folder 7: 35)
      - Popkin, Alice Brandeis (Box-folder 7: 36)
      - Pritchard, James B., Prof. (Box-folder 7: 37)
      - Pugliese, Joe (Box-folder 7: 38)
      - Ramel, Baron Stig (Box-folder 7: 39)
      - Sands, Harold W. (brochure is enclosed) (Box-folder 7: 40)
      - Sherwood, Bob (Box-folder 7: 41)
      - Spafford, Cynthia (Box-folder 7: 42)
      - Sydow, Kristian von (Box-folder 7: 43)
      - Tandberg, Olof G. (Box-folder 7: 44)
      - Vines, E.V. (Box-folder 7: 45)
      - Wellons, Caroline (Box-folder 7: 46)
      - Wilson, Louis H. (Box-folder 7: 47)
    - Memoranda
      - Undated (Box-folder 7: 48)
      - June (Box-folder 7: 49)
      - August (Box-folder 7: 50)
      - September (Box-folder 7: 51)
      - October (Box-folder 7: 52)
      - November (Box-folder 7: 53)
      - Printed matter in Swedish, December (Box-folder 7: 54)
    - Newsletters (Box-folder 7: 55)
    - Notes (Box-folder 7: 56)
    - Schedules
      - March (Box-folder 7: 57)
      - June (Box-folder 7: 58)
      - September (Box-folder 7: 59)
      - October (Box-folder 7: 60)
      - November (Box-folder 7: 61)
      - December (Box-folder 7: 62)
    - Telegrams
      - June (Box-folder 7: 63)
      - (handwritten notes are enclosed), September (Box-folder 7: 64)
      - October (Box-folder 7: 65)
      - November (Box-folder 7: 66)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 7: 67)
    - Printed matter (Box-folder 7: 68)
  - 1978
    - Correspondence
      - Unidentified (mostly handwritten) (Box-folder 8: 1)
      - Abrahamson, Dean, Prof. (Box-folder 8: 2)
      - Adams, Robert M., Dr. (Box-folder 8: 3)
      - Allard, Henry, Honorable (Box-folder 8: 4)
      - Almark, Per, Minister (Box-folder 8: 5)
      - Almen, John, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 8: 6)
      - American Consulate General (Box-folder 8: 7)
      - Anderson, Robert O., Mr. (Box-folder 8: 8)
      - Anderson, Wendell R., Honorable (Box-folder 8: 9)
      - Andrews, Ike F., Honorable (Box-folder 8: 10)
      - Apple, "Johnny" R.W., Mr. (Box-folder 8: 11)
      - Arnesen, Leif, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 12)
      - Aronowitz, Leonard, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 13)
      - Ashley, Thomas Ludlow, M.C. (Box-folder 8: 14)
      - Esling, Nils G., Minister (Box-folder 8: 15)
      - Baldwin, Harry (Box-folder 8: 16)
      - Barbieri, Albert (Box-folder 8: 17)
      - Baydur, Mehmet, Honorable (Box-folder 8: 18)
      - Beard, Robin L., Honorable (Box-folder 8: 19)
      - Bennett, Tapley, Ambassador and Mrs. (Box-folder 8: 20)
      - Bensinger, Peter B. (memorandum is enclosed) (Box-folder 8: 21)
      - Benson, Lucy Wilson (Box-folder 8: 22)
      - Berg, Anton, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 8: 23)
      - Berg, Stephanie, Mrs. (Box-folder 8: 24)